Guide to the Christopher Cox Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1963-1990, undated; Series I; 4.17; (10 boxes)
  - Playwrights Horizons, 1973-1980, undated (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Preston, John, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    Includes "Our People are Dying," his essay on AIDS.
  - Psychology Today, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Publisher's Weekly, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Read, John, 1983, undated (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Richard, Jeremy, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Robert Samuel Gallery, 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Roditi, Edouard, 1985 Mar 29 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Rolling Stone, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Rosenthal, Clement, 1977 Sep 20 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Rorem, Ned, 1974-1981 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Roy, Philippe, 1975-1981, undated (Box 6, Folder 130-131)
  - St. Martin's Press, 1978-1987 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Sacks, Oliver, 1983 Apr 23 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - Sauguet, Henri, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - Screen Actors Guild, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - The Sentinel, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Sinclair, Madge, 1971, undated (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Slaff, Bertram
    See: Dowell, Coleman
  - Soho News, 1980, undated (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Sontag, Susan, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Spin, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Stewart, Leora, 1979-1980, undated (Box 6, Folder 141)
    Contains a snapshot photograph of Cox
  - Stickney, Dorothy, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 142)
    Includes notes of Cox's interview with the actress
  - Strong, Jonathan, 1983-1987 (Box 6, Folder 143)
    Includes Cox's editorial comments on Strong's novel Elsewhere (Ballantine Books, 1985)
  - Suarez, Virgil F., 1990 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Sullivan, Jeffrey, 1975, undated (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Tally, Justine, 1967-1968, undated (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Taylor, William (Bill), 1968-1969, undated (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Thomson, Virgil
    See: Series IV
  - Todd, Terry, 1985 Sep 2 (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - Tonkin, Leo S., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Travel & Leisure, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    See also: Brazil
  - United States Congress, 1966-1984 (Box 7, Folder 151)
    Includes letters from members of the House and Senate regarding employment and legislation
  - Vanity Fair, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - Vetere, Richard, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Vogue, 1987, undated (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - Wallace, George C., undated (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Washington Post, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Watts, Joe, 1978, undated (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - Weidenfeld & Nicolson
    See: Cooper, Dennis
  - Wein, Glenn, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Weston, Cole, 1980 Apr 14 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - White, Edmund
    - Letters to and from Christopher Cox, 1978-1986, undated (Box 7, Folder 160)
    - Letters to and from others, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 161)
    - Interviews, 1978, 1981
    - Reviews and readings
      - Nocturnes for the King of Naples, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 162)
      - States of Desire, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 163)
    - Writings
      - Essays and book reviews published in periodicals, 1979-1981
      - Miscellaneous, manuscripts and typescripts, undated (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Whitmore, George, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Yancey, Donna, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Yorty, Don, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Zajonc, Margaret (Peg), 1976-1977, undated (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Zinn, Randolyn, 1978, undated (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - Zupruk, Bob, 1970, undated (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - [Unidentified], Roy, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - General correspondence
    - Letters and mailings (labeled by Cox "before 1968"), 1965, undated (Box 8, Folder 172)
    - Letters and mailings, 1968-1976 (Box 8, Folder 173-182)
    - Letters and mailings, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 177-186)
    - Employment, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 187)
    - Letters and mailings, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 188-193)
    - Letters and mailings, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 194-196)
    - Birthday party invitation and cards, 1984 Aug (Box 10, Folder 197)
    - Holiday cards, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 198)
    - Mailings, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 199)
    - Letters and mailings, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 200-203)
    - Letters, undated, 1980s (Box 10, Folder 204)
    - Photography [sales correspondence and invoices], 1979-1986 (Box 10, Folder 205)
    - Unsent cards and postcards, undated (Box 10, Folder 206)
- Creative Work, 1969-1989, undated; Series II; 3.34; (8 boxes)
  Organized into two subseries: Writings and Performances.
  The first subseries, Writings, is arranged under five headings: Articles and Essays; Novels; Stories; Video and Film Projects; and Miscellaneous material related to his compositions. The second subseries, Performances, contains files on theatrical events in which Cox participated, as either an actor, singer, or director. It excludes his work with the Joseph Jefferson Theatre Company, all of which is filed in Series V.
  The first group of Writings, Articles and Essays, has a selection of Cox's non-fiction work, some of which may have been published, though there are only two examples of articles that appeared in print. Here too are three files on the Chelsea Hotel which document his interest in writing an article (and then a book) on the place that was his home from 1982 to 1985, but he abandoned the project when he learned that a picture book on the residence had been released. The folders contain drafts of his essays as well as his research material, including transcripts of interviews he held with Stanley Bard, the hotel's manager from the 1950s through 2007, and a long-time resident, Mildred Baker. The Novels section has material related to four unfinished novels for which Cox had set up series of files to hold his drafts and notes. Most of the projects drew their storylines from personal experiences: "Alabama" is based on his childhood memories; "Doe's Pillow" has references to characters he encountered in the South; "Gay Sapho" [sic] is a roman à clef which concerns his affair and breakup with Edmund White; and "Dreams from a Biology Classroom" was inspired by his mother's death from cancer. The Stories section also has files he set up, which contain tales largely drawn from his personal experiences. Also among these is "The Sounds of his Childhood," which is about his partner Bill Olander, and includes a draft of a letter Cox wrote to Edmund White about Olander. "The Magic of Buddy Simms" takes place in Key West, and its folder contains Cox's notes on corrections and additions for future editions of his 1983 Key West book.
  It is unclear whether Cox ever submitted any of his works of fiction to publishers, with the exception of "Memory/Winterdance"; that file has an undated letter of rejection from The Saturday Evening Post. A version of his story "Aunt Persia and the Jesus Man," was published after his death in the anthology The Violet Quill Reader (1994).
  The Video and Film Projects section has files with Cox's plans, notes, scripts, and storyboards for a number of works, some of which reuse content from his other writings, while others, such as "Happy Love Has No History," are autobiographical in nature. Cox was a founder of Endless Sleep Productions, a self-described "informally structured collective of writers/directors/performers banded together for mutual assistance in producing individual works." The other members were William Dolson, Philippe Roy, and Margaret (Peg) Zajonc. A folder in this section has descriptions of nine proposed video pieces, and according to one of his resumes in Series III (Box 23, Folder 393), Cox's video, "The Canary Wears Bangs" was shown at the Birmingham [Alabama] Arts Festival in 1977. The last folder in the subseries was titled by Cox "Notes for new video pieces" and has a multi-page and untitled narrative for another autobiographical work featuring Edmund White and George Morris.
  Aside from his personal history, some of Cox's other inspirations are evident in the production folders: "The Bleeding Scissors" holds a battered 1955 paperback edition of Bruno Fischer's 1948 book of the same title, and "The Salad Dressing Murder" has newspaper clippings about a slain Alabama coed whose body was found near a grocery bag holding a bottle of salad dressing.
  The subseries Performances holds files on theatrical and film productions in which Cox was involved as a director, actor, collaborator, or technician. Dames at Sea has only a set of handwritten notes on lighting, while two productions in which Cox was a member of a touring company, Jesus Christ Superstar and Two Gentlemen of Verona, include programs and pay stubs. The largest group of files exists for A Christmas Carol, a version of the Charles Dickens story conceived and directed by Cox, and presented at the Queens [New York] Festival Theatre in late 1977. Two of the productions, Blood from the Heart of America and The Company Stow, were collaborative events based on texts by Doug Dyer with lyrics by company members including Cox. The folder for the James Joyce Memorial Liquid Theatre, (a 1972 work of performance art at the Guggenheim Museum that was subtitled "an experiment in making people feel good") contains a set of pastel drawings of the cast members.
  - Writings
    - Articles and essays
      - "Art Smart" [on Keith Haring], in Us Magazine, 1986 Mar 10 (Box 11, Folder 207)
      - Chelsea Hotel project, typescripts and research notes, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 208-210)
      - "Montecatini—Italy's Splendid Spa" [Capri], in Travel & Leisure, 1984 Mar (Box 11, Folder 211)
      - [On Robby Anton], typescript, circa 1984 (Box 11, Folder 212)
      - [On Aaron Copland], typescript carbon, undated (Box 11, Folder 213)
      - [On Candy Darling], typescripts and notes, circa 1974 (Box 11, Folder 214)
      - [On Coleman Dowell], notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 215)
      - [On Maurice Grosser], typescripts, undated (Box 11, Folder 216)
      - [On Dorothea Lange], annotated typescripts, undated (Box 11, Folder 217)
      - [On Sherrie Levine], manuscript notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 218)
      - [On Louis/Evidence of Friendship], typescripts, undated (Box 11, Folder 219)
      - [On George Morris], typescripts, undated (Box 11, Folder 220)
      - [On the New York Institute for the Humanities], typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 221)
      - [Review of Saul's Book, by Paul Rogers], typescript, undated (Box 11, Folder 222)
      - Ideas for articles, undated (Box 11, Folder 223)
    - Novels
      - "Alabama," manuscripts, typescripts, and notes
        - Billy Ballou, undated (Box 12, Folder 224)
        - Billy Striplin, undated (Box 12, Folder 225)
        - The Cemetery, undated (Box 12, Folder 226)
        - The Drive through Gadsden, undated (Box 12, Folder 227)
        - Funeral food, 1980, undated (Box 12, Folder 228)
        - Gadsden, undated (Box 12, Folder 229)
        - Grandmama Cox, undated (Box 12, Folder 230)
        - The Happy Roebucks, undated (Box 12, Folder 231)
        - Opening - chapter 1, undated (Box 12, Folder 232)
        - Pensacola (Gracious Living in Pensacola), undated (Box 12, Folder 233)
        - Reunion, undated (Box 12, Folder 234)
        - Sandusky Road, undated (Box 12, Folder 235)
        - Satellite, undated (Box 12, Folder 236)
        - Uncle Roy, undated (Box 12, Folder 237)
        - Weathergirl, undated (Box 12, Folder 238)
        - Miscellaneous notes and drafts, undated (Box 12, Folder 239-242)
      - "Doe's Pillow," manuscripts, typescripts, and notes
        - After the fight, undated (Box 13, Folder 243)
        - Character notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 244)
        - Descriptive story and notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 245)
        - Fancy and Persia in bedroom, undated (Box 13, Folder 246)
        - Final scene, undated (Box 13, Folder 247)
        - Original story, undated (Box 13, Folder 248)
        - Outlines, undated (Box 13, Folder 249)
        - Tent, 1979, undated (Box 13, Folder 250)
        - Trailer, undated (Box 13, Folder 251)
        - Notes and drafts, undated (Box 13, Folder 252-261)
      - "Dreams from a Biology Classroom," manuscripts, typescripts, and notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 262-263)
      - "Gay Sapho," [sic] manuscripts, typescripts, and notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 264-265)
    - Stories
      - "Aunt Persia and the Jesus Man," typescripts and notes, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 266)
      - "Curtains," manuscript and typescripts, undated (Box 14, Folder 267)
      - "Cut Up," assemblage of newspapers texts, undated (Box 14, Folder 268)
      - "History is Made at Night," typescripts and notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 269)
      - "Inventing Edmund," typed outline, undated (Box 14, Folder 270)
      - "The Late Afternoons of Solly Broom," typescripts and notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 271)
      - "Living for History," notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 272)
      - "The Magic of Buddy Simms (Key West Story)," typescripts and notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 273)
      - "Memory/Winterdance," typescripts, 1969, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 274)
      - "Miami Morgue," typescripts and notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 275)
      - "The New Ocean," manuscript notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 276)
      - "Shit," typescript, undated (Box 14, Folder 277)
      - "The Sounds of his Childhood," manuscripts, typescripts, and notes, circa 1989 (Box 14, Folder 278)
    - Video and film projects
      - "Black Soup on the Nile"
        - Production notes, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 279-280)
        - Storyboard and script, undated (Box 15, Folder 281)
        - Scripts, undated (Box 15, Folder 282-283)
      - "The Bleeding Scissors," manuscript and typescript notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 284)
        Includes copy of paperback novel
      - "The Bouillabaise Ball," manuscript and typescript notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 285)
      - "The Canary Wears Bangs"
        - Casting and finances, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 286)
        - Editing notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 287)
        - Production notes, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 288)
        - Storyboard, undated (Box 15, Folder 289)
      - "Carnival Glass," manuscript and typescript notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 290)
      - [Dinner Party], manuscript notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 291)
      - Endless Sleep Productions, manuscript notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 292)
      - "Happy Love Has No History," typescripts and notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 293)
      - "The Ice Cremation of a Lunar Moth in Violent Weather," typescript and manuscript notes, [1971?] (Box 16, Folder 294)
      - "In the Basilica of the Virgin of Guadalupe," manuscript and typescript notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 295)
      - "Mojave Teenagers for Christ," manuscript and typescript notes, 1976, undated (Box 16, Folder 296)
      - "Neurotic Moon"
        See also: "Nightwaitress," Box 16, Folder 299
        - Production notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 297)
        - Scripts, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 298)
      - "Nightwaitress," manuscript and typescript notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 299)
      - "The Salad Dressing Murder," manuscript and typsecript notes, storyboard, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 300)
      - "Slur: A Performance Piece," manuscript and typescript notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 301)
      - Notes for new video pieces, undated (Box 16, Folder 302)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Expressions and slang, undated (Box 16, Folder 303)
      - Notebooks, undated (Box 16, Folder 304)
      - Project ideas
        - Manuscript and typescript notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 305-308)
        - Newspaper clippings, 1974-1981 (Box 16, Folder 309)
      - Story titles, undated (Box 16, Folder 310)
  - Performances
    - Blood from the Heart of America, by Doug Dyer
      - Scripts and notes, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 311-313)
      - Song lyrics, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 314)
      - Publicity and reviews, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 315)
    - BMI workshops, 1971-1974 (Box 17, Folder 316)
    - A Christmas Carol, conceived by Christopher Cox
      - Casts and auditions, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 317)
      - Production notes, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 318)
      - Programs and publicity, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 319)
      - Scripts
        - First draft, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 320)
        - Second draft #1, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 321)
        - Second draft #2, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 322)
        - Miscellaneous drafts, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 323)
    - The Company Stow, by Doug Dyer, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 324)
    - Dames at Sea, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 325)
    - Fan Fare, by Lloyd Birdwell, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 326)
    - James Joyce Memorial Liquid Theatre, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 327)
    - Jesus Christ Superstar, by Andrew Lloyd Webber and Tim Rice, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 328)
    - Lucifer, by Chuck Pennington and Bob Rozgay
      - Script, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 329)
      - Production notes and reviews, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 330)
    - Medea, by Jean Anouilh, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 331)
    - Pretty Baby, by Louis Malle, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 332)
    - Storkwood, by Mark Dunster, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 333)
    - Two Gentlemen of Verona, by William Shakespeare, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 334)
    - Uncommon Women and Others, by Wendy Wasserstein, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 335)
    - We Bombed in New Haven, by Joseph Heller, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 336)
    - Witness for the Prosecution, by Agatha Christie
      - Leases, contracts, finances, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 337)
      - Production notes, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 338)
      - Advertisement, 1975 Aug 7
- Personal Papers, 1935-1990, undated; Series III; 2.92; (7 boxes)
  Organized into two subseries: Diaries and Family Papers; the latter is organized into three sections: Raymond Cox Jr. Papers; Family Correspondence; and Family Documents.
  The first subseries, Diaries, holds Cox's own records of his life, beginning with seventeen volumes of his diaries and daybooks, covering the years 1960, 1964, 1965, and 1968 through 1980. They are commercial diaries and planners in which Cox recorded varying amounts of information: some have just appointments and brief notes about meetings (including dinners, listing his fellow diners), while in others, such as his 1968 book, he recorded world events and his thoughts about them. The subseries Journal Notes is a set of files organized and labeled by Cox. They cover the years from "Before 1964" through 1978, and have individual sheets of paper on which he wrote or typed narratives that are part diary, part memoir, and part short story, along with some letters he received. Many of the events and situations appear later in his creative writings. Added to the subseries are two bound blank books which were found in with miscellaneous material, each with just two pages of autobiographical narrative written in Cox's hand.
  The subseries Family Papers is arranged in three groups: Raymond Cox Jr. Documents; Family Correspondence; and Family Documents, which hold papers about, to, and from Cox and his family of origin. The first section contains documents ranging from Cox's baptism records to his high school diploma and prom photographs, some college material, and papers relating to his life in New York City, including his resumes and autobiographical statements. The second section, Family Correspondence, has letters to Cox from his parents, sisters, brother, uncle, and grandmothers. There is also one file of letters from Cox to his grandparents and parents. Family Documents holds some school records for Cox's mother, Dorothy Trusler Cox, which are among the earliest papers in the collection, as well as the diary of his paternal grandmother, and some miscellaneous genealogical material, including a family chart drawn out by Cox. The file on Cox's uncle Roy, a veteran of both World War II and Korea who committed suicide at age 31 in 1956, holds photographs, a newspaper obituary, and sympathy notes from family friends; Roy Cox figures prominently in Christopher Cox's creative writings, particularly his novel "Alabama."
  There are few photographs of Cox found in the collection, and most appear in random locations within this series.
  One notable personal document in Cox's papers is a typewritten and partial last will and testament that he signed on March 4, 1980. Though it might logically have been filed in this series, the item remains where he had placed it, in with Edmund White's letters in Series I. The document specifies Cox's wishes for his the disposition of his photographs, negatives, papers, cats, and ashes, though he did not name an executor, finish the document, or have it notarized or witnessed.
  - Diaries
    - Daybooks and calendars, 1960-1974 (Box 19, Folder 339-344)
    - Daybooks and calendars, 1975-1979 (Box 20, Folder 345-347)
    - Expense diary (notes), 1986 (Box 20, Folder 348)
    - Journal notes
      - "Before 1964", circa 1964 (Box 21, Folder 349)
      - Notes, 1966-1978 (Box 21, Folder 350-364)
    - Memoir, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 365)
    - Memoir, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 366)
  - Family papers
    - Raymond Cox Jr. papers
      - Baptism records, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 367)
      - School records, 1955-1967 (Box 22, Folder 368)
      - Class photo album, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 369)
      - Arithmetic workbook, circa 1957 (Box 22, Folder 370)
      - Poems, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 371)
      - Artwork, 1957, undated (Box 22, Folder 372)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1957-1972 (Box 22, Folder 373)
      - Church camp material, 1963-1965 (Box 22, Folder 374)
      - School photographs, 1963-1967 (Box 22, Folder 375)
      - School ephemera, 1964-1965, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 376)
      - School newspaper clippings, 1965-1966, undated (Box 22, Folder 377)
      - White House seminar program and ticket, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 378)
      - High school diploma, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 379)
      - Senior class album, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 380)
      - University of Alabama
        - Playbills and identification card, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 381)
        - Delta Tau Delta material, 1968, 1978, undated (Box 23, Folder 382)
        - Miscellaneous campus publications, 1967-1969 (Box 23, Folder 383)
      - Identification, library, and other cards, 1967-1985 (Box 23, Folder 384)
      - United States, Selective Service System, 1968-1972 (Box 23, Folder 385)
      - HB Studio card and receipts, 1969 Sep (Box 23, Folder 386)
      - David Frost Show personnel directory, 1969 Nov (Box 23, Folder 387)
      - Auditions, 1971-1972, undated (Box 23, Folder 388)
      - Health and finance papers, 1971-1990 (Box 23, Folder 389)
      - Unemployment forms, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 390)
      - Vital records and passport photographs, 1977, undated (Box 23, Folder 391)
      - Astrology reading notes, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 392)
      - Resumes and autobiographical statements, 1978, 1981, undated (Box 23, Folder 393)
      - Astrology chart and notes, 1985 Jan 17 (Box 23, Folder 394)
      - Psychic reading notes, 1986 Dec 7 (Box 23, Folder 395)
      - Lease and correspondence, 130 West 23rd Street, 1976-1984, undated (Box 23, Folder 396-398)
      - Lease and correspondence, Chelsea Hotel, 1982-1985 (Box 23, Folder 399)
      - Address books, undated (Box 23, Folder 400)
      - Address and phone number notes and cards, undated (Box 23, Folder 401)
      - Miscellaneous notes, phone messages, etc., undated (Box 23, Folder 402)
    - Family correspondence
      - Carlisle, Carol Cox and Danny, 1970-1984, undated (Box 24, Folder 403-406)
      - Cox, Dorothy Trusler, 1962-1975, undated (Box 24, Folder 407-409)
      - Cox, Nancy Trusler, 1967-1986, undated (Box 24, Folder 410)
      - Cox, Raymond Jr., letters to family members, 1964-1976, undated (Box 25, Folder 411)
      - Cox, Raymond Sr., 1966-1982, undated (Box 25, Folder 412)
      - Cox, Timothy Wade, 1960-1981 (Box 25, Folder 413)
      - Cox, Willie Broom, 1969-1982, undated (Box 25, Folder 414-415)
      - Trusler, Gladys F., 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 416)